cpfc.org 2003-04-09

# Privacy Statement for CPFC BBS

### Privacy Statement for [www.cpfc.org](http://www.cpfc.org/)

CPFC Bulletin Board Services has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: CPFC BBS.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, and for other purposes.

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

  * Unsubscribe from links updates <http://www.cpfc.org/links/cgi-bin/subscribe.cgi>
  * Unsubscribe from forum updates <http://www.cpfc.org/cgi-bin/ubbcgi/ubbmisc.cgi?action=setprefs>
  * Unsubscribe from Private messages <http://www.cpfc.org/cgi-bin/ubbcgi/privateprefs.cgi>

This site contains links to other sites. [www.cpfc.org](http://www.cpfc.org/)  is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

### Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Our server are continually monitored.

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor.

### Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  * You can update your profile by visiting [http://www.cpfc.org/cgi-bin/ubbcgi/ubbmisc.cgi?action=editbio&Browser](http://www.cpfc.org/cgi-bin/ubbcgi/ubbmisc.cgi?action=editbio&Browser)

_CPFC Bulletin Board Services works with a third party that serves ads to this site. To find out more about how Amazing Media manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to<http://amazingmedia.com/company/privacy.jsp>._

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us   [staff@cpfc.org](mailto:staff@cpfc.org)
